<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on handWritten . POLIW.AT</title>
    <link>https://hands.poliw.at/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on handWritten . POLIW.AT</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 23:50:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://hands.poliw.at/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It All Started With My Hands and My Hands Never Failed</title>
      <link>https://hands.poliw.at/it-all-started-with-my-hands-and-my-hands-never-failed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 23:50:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hands.poliw.at/it-all-started-with-my-hands-and-my-hands-never-failed/</guid>
      <description>1151pm
yet ahahahaha  worked all day on    🌏.fm  S
qq qqqxxqxqxqq]qqqxxqxqxqq
 worked all day on sunny day coded n uploaded av n downloaded native instruments n spliff in alleyway with cam n g and ts n next pbd ep question n found n all nighter inbound  sunny day coded n uploaded av n downloaded native instruments n spliff in alleyway with cam n g and ts n next pbd ep question n found n all nighter inbound  WHEN HASAS VAE MY HANDS EVR FIALED ME ?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>G and T Nonprofit Hackathon</title>
      <link>https://hands.poliw.at/g-and-t-nonprofit-hackathon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 20:58:34 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hands.poliw.at/g-and-t-nonprofit-hackathon/</guid>
      <description>=-==-=—=-=-=-=
tuesday 858pm
there are only 2 types of people in this world but i don’t remember cause we went to the next conversational subject
=-==-=-=&amp;ndash;=-==
he&amp;rsquo;s not on a 3 day plan schedule
Throw them in the amazon prime waterboarding device for 299 and 99.9% of those interrogated speak within 7 minutes. Used to be 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If Then That Us Wakeup Danceparty</title>
      <link>https://hands.poliw.at/if-then-that-us-wakeup-danceparty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 11:13:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hands.poliw.at/if-then-that-us-wakeup-danceparty/</guid>
      <description>1113AM
on a good one right now, but terbz behind. not going to leave NB aside from body and gear needs.
going to setup PBD tv today and finish all the websites and won&amp;rsquo;t leave until they&amp;rsquo;re all done
BUT cam is going to smoke a tiny spliff at the top of dolo by the statue at 1130 and I could jog there real quick &amp;hellip;. and the sun is shining bright so I might do that quickly cause I left my laptop charger here as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miles Davis 4Loco Freestyle NightTimeBestTime</title>
      <link>https://hands.poliw.at/miles-davis-4loco-freestyle-nighttimebesttime/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 00:16:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hands.poliw.at/miles-davis-4loco-freestyle-nighttimebesttime/</guid>
      <description>migrate =&amp;gt;
juul video
each person I meet i become real close to them then they hit the vape once and die
all these good looking people hit the vape and die but when I hit the vape I just feel good father yes son I want to kill you
&amp;lt;=
got 1219AM
feels so good to be back on osx omg
142am
IF YOU ARE TALKING TO ME WHEN I POLIW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Happens After the Full Send</title>
      <link>https://hands.poliw.at/what-happens-after-the-full-send/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2019 15:41:16 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hands.poliw.at/what-happens-after-the-full-send/</guid>
      <description>9pm @ NB
freestyled with will and the dude that was an asshole last time but he was pretty nice this time ahahahahah men
Im not going to lie - I feel fucking lost right now
just freestyled and then found myself in the turing room, a combo between anarchist graffiti walls and fluorescent lighting from walmart
its quiet here and the only album I need now is
=-=-=-=-=-=-=-=
sunday</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HandDrawn Quantify and NothingDamn Else</title>
      <link>https://hands.poliw.at/handdrawn-quantify-and-nothingdamn-else/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 11:35:15 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hands.poliw.at/handdrawn-quantify-and-nothingdamn-else/</guid>
      <description>alright the same schema gotta go down I know it
ahahahahahh these people are so fucking cool I know it in my bones
context quantify poliw.at poliw.at vitals
 some 50s hippies  like %%^&amp;****  - days out  What Now  =&amp;ndash;==-=&amp;ndash;=-=-=-=-=
then my radio show is tonight but if I get the macbook then Im just going to have charlotte hit play for me on my show then I&amp;rsquo;ll install mashine and ableton and full send on that workflow stuff</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Did It All Start With</title>
      <link>https://hands.poliw.at/what-did-it-all-start-with/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 11:23:09 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hands.poliw.at/what-did-it-all-start-with/</guid>
      <description>1125 AM
was jogging a bit with ghost but then all of a sudden,
CRAZY GUY OUTSIDE THE COFFEE SHOP oh yeah we were in the coffeeeshoppp
Ive been handwriting poliwat on this clipboard I spray painted red months ago and it&amp;rsquo;s been a nice calming change of pace. Hands.poliw.at is the new brain dump
but stayed up till like 4-5 am don&amp;rsquo;t remember making this site, and then made the song site too cause that&amp;rsquo;s real needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Hands Have Turnt</title>
      <link>https://hands.poliw.at/these-hands-have-learned/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 03:50:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hands.poliw.at/these-hands-have-learned/</guid>
      <description>0341pm
and what hands have these turnt ?
I made this because I sold my windows laptop so just have SMs other old lappy with ubuntu - peter wouldnt help me today and I have been spending a lot of time trying to get a good recording rig going. God is laughing at me but I&amp;rsquo;m used to it
I AM BACK ON after %%^&amp;****  - days out  What Now  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>tEHES HANDS</title>
      <link>https://hands.poliw.at/birth-of-handsy.poliwat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 03:41:17 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hands.poliw.at/birth-of-handsy.poliwat/</guid>
      <description>0341pm
I AM BACK ON after %%^&amp;****  - days out  Text secondary Dashed Thick  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>